Marina Yamamoto

Vancouver, BC | marina.vamamoto8@gmail.com

Portfolio: marinayamamoto.ca | LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/marina-yamamoto-558276128

SUMMARY

I've worked as a graphic designer for 9+ years and currently working as a web designer and front-end developer for 2+ years. I have experience collaborating with external teams such as marketing, product, and management to plan, strategize and execute features.

I was in charge of planning and producing advertisements, magazines, and general promotional materials.

EXPERIENCE

Web / Graphic Designer

Symply Cubed Inc., IT security — Tokyo, Japan — Part-time

Feb 2021 - May 2021

- · Branding for internal and external use
- Created a new design for the website and gave a presentation
- Created internal materials to unify brand awareness

Web / Graphic Designer

Paidy Inc., Financial Services — Tokyo, Japan — Full-time

May 2018 – Jan 2020

[Designed corporate site]

- Designed new web pages and sections with customer and business pages, made all icons and illustrations [Involved in company branding]
- Helped unify the brand image both internally and externally by creating design systems, and logo guidelines
- Managed event booth design and flyers

Online Advertisement Designer

Cyber Agent Inc., Web Advertising Agency — Tokyo, Japan — Full-time

Dec 2017 - Apr 2018

[Designed web banner advertisements]

- Designed in-feed advertisements of major corporations. (e.g. Samsung, Rakuten, Rotte)
- Redesigned banners in required formats in a short time. (e.g. 50 resize banners in a day)

Graphic Designer / Art Director

First Publicity Inc., Marketing & Advertising — Tokyo, Japan — Full-time

Apr 2011 - Jun 2017

[Designed magazine of Japan Nailist Association]

- · Involved in conferences as writer and editor
- Art direction of cover and opening visual pages

[Concept development and designed events posters, pamphlets, and contents]

- Involved in events as writer and editor and made report pages in the magazine
- Directed the photographers to ensure that all necessary photos were taken smoothly within the limited time [Managed schedules of pamphlets of fashion]
- Contacted everyone involved in the production to manage the shooting samples and schedule

SKILLS

Figma, Sketch Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign HTML, CSS, Javascript Typography

EDUCATION

Web Development / CICCC - Cornerstone International Community College of Canada — Vancouver Sep 2020 - Aug 2021

Graphic Designer / Toyo Institute Of Art & Design — Tokyo, Japan

Apr 2009 - Mar 2011